Come to the work of someone in pain and throw someone who is drowning
This look is a must
Put it on someone unfortunate
Come to the work of someone in pain and throw someone who is drowning
This look is a must
Put it on someone unfortunate
I don't know about mosques, I don't know about temples
Accept my humility
Give me more pain
Come to the work of someone in pain and throw someone who is drowning
This look is a must Put it on someone unfortunate -,,
This is Mekshi's pride, this is the servant of my heart
May my Mekda continue and give beauty to my servants
Come to the work of someone in pain and throw someone who is drowning
This look is a must Put it on someone unfortunate -,,
What should I do with your separation? This is the death of my horrors
May your madness come upon me
Take me out of Paradise
Come to the work of someone in pain and throw someone who is drowning
This look is a must Put it on someone unfortunate